# Alex Hawley

4518 Winlock San Antonio, Texas, 78228 2102142245 asimo124@yahoo.com

### **Professional Summary**

Senior PHP Developer with 10 years experience in PHP Web Development. Worked in depth with the PHP Symfony Framework. Strong work ethic, and comfortable in a team environment. Have worked in depth with complex PHP Web Applications. Quick learner and always wanting to learn new technologies such as ReactJS and Angular.

#### Personal Information

Raised in San Antonio. Musician. Enjoy playing in APA Pool League.

#### Skills

- PHP
- MySQL with Stored Procedures
- Symphony PHP Framework
- Full Stack Capabilities

## Work Experience

#### VISUAL NET DESIGN, SAN ANTONIO, TEXAS

Web Developer, Jan 2008 - Aug 2016

- Worked on large-scale websites for big clients.
- Worked on a team, while managing other programmers to bring projects to completion.

#### DIGITAL BEEF, SAN ANTONIO, TEXAS

Web and iOS Developer, Aug 2016 - Feb 2017

- Main developer involved in coding the iOS version of the Company App.
  - Worked in a team maintaining the cattle records websites, using PHP and Postgresql, including working with large datasets.

#### CLAIMATIC, SAN ANTONIO, TEXAS

Senior Web Developer, Feb 2017 - Present

■ Both maintained an Insurance SAAS Web Application, as well as worked on the development of a new version, using the PHP Symfony Framework, with MySQL.

## Education

#### SAN ANTONIO COLLEGE, SAN ANTONIO, TEXAS

Completed coursework towards Associate Degree in Computer Science, May 2004

■ Completed courses towards an Associate Degree in Computer Science.

## Additional Skills

- 10 years of experience in PHP MySQL with Stored Procedures
- 1 year of experience with PHP Symfony Framework, with strong interest in Laravel
- Studied Front End Frameworks like Angular and ReactJS
- 8 years of experience with using Linux Shell
- 6 years of experience with Bash/Shell Scripting
- 1 year of experience writing iOS Apps with Swift
- Postgresql experience